Brother Cornelius Russell Papers
Marist College Archives and Special Collections
- 2. Photographic Material, 1900 - 2009; 2; Boxes: 7 Folders: 80 - 95
  - Brother Cornelius, Family and close friend Prayer cards., 1900 November - 2009 October (Folder 92, Box 7)
  - Marist Brother Prayer Cards, 1959 July - 2008 April (Folder 93, Box 7)
  - Prayer Cards, Undated (Folder 94, Box 7)
  - Miscellaneous Photos: Nursing home Photos, Family members, 1977-2007 (Folder 95, Box 7)
- 3. Textile Material, 1942; 3; Box: 8 Folder: 96
  - WWII uniform jacket and shirt, Circa 1942 (Folder 96, Box 8)
- 4. Personal Materials, 4; Box: 9 Folders: 97 - 101
  Series contains physical personal materials including VHS tapes, a plate, uniform pins, an American flad, and an anitque frame.
  - Heritage Professors VHS, Circa 2003 (Folder 97, Box 9)
  - Brother Cornelius name plate, Undated (Folder 98, Box 9)
  - Pins from Uniform: Rank Stripes (Tec. Sergeant), Circa 1943 (Folder 99, Box 9)
  - Small American Flag, Undated (Folder 100, Box 9)
  - Antique Frame ( see box 6), Circa 1900 (Folder 101, Box 9)